{
    "subject": "resource/Salah_Mansour",
    "predicate": "property/deathDate",
    "object": "1979-01-19",
    "human_readable": "Salah Mansour died on January 19th, 1979.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9015853404998779,
            "question": "When did Salah Mansour die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8105331659317017,
            "question": "What year was Salah Mansour's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6844418048858643,
            "question": "What was the cause of Salah Mansour's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6338016390800476,
            "question": "Were there any notable events associated with Salah Mansour's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.602587103843689,
            "question": "Is there any information about Salah Mansour's life before his death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5347429513931274,
            "question": "On what date did Salah Mansour pass away?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48450616002082825,
            "question": "Was Salah Mansour known for anything specific?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4286639392375946,
            "question": "Can you provide more details about Salah Mansour?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3842456340789795,
            "question": "Are there any sources that provide more information about Salah Mansour?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37781476974487305,
            "question": "Can you tell me anything else about Salah Mansour's life?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Salah Mansour died on January 19th, 1979.",
            "html": "dbpedia_219_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any sources that provide more information about Salah Mansour?",
            "html": "dbpedia_219_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide more details about Salah Mansour?",
            "html": "dbpedia_219_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Salah Mansour known for anything specific?",
            "html": "dbpedia_219_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_219_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_219_144.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_219_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_219_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_219_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_219_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_219_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_219_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_219_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_219_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer:\n\n{\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nExplanation: The documents contain information about Salah Mansour's death date, specifically stating that he \"died on January 19 1979.\" This supports the triple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that Salah Mansour died on January 19, 1979."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}